[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0100_d_00_container_brimstoneundersiege",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p1",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 30,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0100_brimstoneundersiege_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0101_thegreatarchitect",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0101_d_00_container_thegreatarchitect",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p1",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 80,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0101_thegreatarchitect_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0102_preemptivestrike",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0102_d_00_container_preemptivestrike",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_02",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0102_preemptivestrike_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Footwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0102_preemptivestrike_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0103_stirringinthesands",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0103_d_00_container_stirringinthesands",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p3",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_03",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0103_stirringinthesands_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "TinctureAcidT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0103_stirringinthesands_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0201_ablossomingthreat",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0201_d_00_container_ablossomingthreat",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p4",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_04",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0201_ablossomingthreat_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0202_pastprologue",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0202_d_00_container_pastprologue",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p4",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0202_pastprologue_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0202_pastprologue_Complete_multi_01",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0301_wateringtheseed",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0301_d_00_container_wateringtheseed",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v1p4",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_06",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0301_wateringtheseed_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_multi_03_Proposal_prompt_01",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_multi_04_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_TalkTo_Ghazi_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0301_wateringtheseed_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0302_unravelingthemystery",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0302_d_00_container_unravelingthemystery",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v2p1",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Chestwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0302_unravelingthemystery_Complete_a_multinpc",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0303_accursedalchemy",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0303_d_00_container_accursedalchemy",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v2p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_08",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0303_accursedalchemy_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Start_multinpc",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0303_accursedalchemy_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0401_thedemonscauldron",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0401_d_00_container_thedemonscauldron",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v2p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0401_thedemonscauldron_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0501_powerofthegods",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0501_d_00_container_powerofthegods",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v2p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0501_powerofthegods_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Headgear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0501_powerofthegods_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0502_d_00_container_scourgeaeonmadness",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p6",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0502_scourgeaeonmadness_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0601_eyeofhorus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0601_d_00_container_eyeofhorus",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1678_EmptyChest",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_12",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0601_eyeofhorus_success",
		"ObjectiveReward": "1625_0701_challengingpharaoh",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Details",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0601_eyeofhorus_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0701_challengingpharaoh",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0701_d_00_container_challengingpharaoh",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v4p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_13",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0701_challengingpharaoh_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0701_challengingpharaoh_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0701_challengingpharaoh_Description",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0701_challengingpharaoh_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0801_agodawakens",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0801_d_00_container_agodawakens",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v4p3",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_14",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0801_agodawakens_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 200,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0801_agodawakens_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_1001_thewildhuntress",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_1001_d_00_container_thewildhuntress",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v4p3",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_19",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_15",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_1001_thewildhuntress_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_1001_thewildhuntress_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1612_0101_praetorians",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1612_0101_d_00_container_praetorians",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1612_Andrea",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_06",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1612_0101_praetorians_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Chestwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1612_0101_praetorians_Title",
		"Description": "@1612_0101_praetorians_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1612_0101_praetorians_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@NPC_Default_Dialogue_1612_01_Clermont_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1612_0101_praetorians_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1612_0101_praetorians_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1612_0201_personaldemons",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1612_0201_d_00_container_personaldemons",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1612_Andrea",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_02",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1612_0201_personaldemons_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1612_0201_1hRoundShield_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Title",
		"Description": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1612_0201_personaldemons_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1612_0301_dutiesmaintained",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1612_0301_d_00_container_dutiesmaintained",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1603_Barnabas",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_03",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Title",
		"Description": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1612_0301_dutiesmaintained_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc3"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1606_0101_lost_manticore",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1606_0101_d_00_container_lost_manticore",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1606_Ambrosius_p2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1606_0101_lost_manticore_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Title",
		"Description": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1606_0101_lost_manticore_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1666_0101_d_00_container_audiencewithpontifex",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1666_Razin",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_30",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_06",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Title",
		"Description": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1666_0101_audiencewithpontifex_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc5"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1604_0101_powerofgods",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1604_0101_d_00_container_powerofgods",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Menefir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_30",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1604_0101_powerofgods_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Title",
		"Description": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1604_0101_powerofgods_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc5"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0101_sleepingvessels",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0101_d_00_container_sleepingvessels",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Menefir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_06",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0101_sleepingvessels_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0101_sleepingvessels_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc5"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0201_immortalgems",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0201_d_00_container_immortalgems",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Menefir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0201_immortalgems_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Runeglass_Case_Empty_Arcane",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0201_immortalgems_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc5"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0301_awakenanubis",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0301_d_00_container_awakenanubis",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Menefir",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_08",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0301_awakenanubis_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1605_0301_2hWarhammer_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0301_awakenanubis_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc5"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0401_insufficientfaith",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0401_d_00_container_insufficientfaith",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1604_Charmion",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0401_insufficientfaith_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0401_insufficientfaith_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1601_0101_cursedcenturies",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1601_0101_d_00_container_cursedcenturies",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1613_Alaina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1601_0101_cursedcenturies_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Title",
		"Description": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1601_0101_cursedcenturies_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1613_0101_assaultlegion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1613_0101_d_00_container_assaultlegion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1613_Alaina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_11",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1613_0101_assaultlegion_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1613_0101_2hSpear_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Title",
		"Description": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1613_0101_assaultlegion_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1613_0201_hydrasbreath",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1613_0201_d_00_container_hydrasbreath",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1613_Alaina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_12",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1613_0201_hydrasbreath_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Title",
		"Description": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1613_0201_hydrasbreath_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1613_0301_blazeofglory",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1613_0301_d_00_container_blazeofglory",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1613_Alaina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_13",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1613_0301_blazeofglory_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1613_0301_2hGreatAxe_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Title",
		"Description": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1613_0301_blazeofglory_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc4"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1613_0401_lastcenturion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1613_0401_d_00_container_lastcenturion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Desert",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_14 && 16_Quest_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1613_0401_lastcenturion_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Title",
		"Description": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1613_0401_lastcenturion_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1613_0501_legendrestored",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1613_0501_d_00_container_legendrestored",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1613_Alaina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_15",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1613_0501_legendrestored_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Title",
		"Description": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1613_0501_legendrestored_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1604_0201_heronomore",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1604_0201_d_00_container_heronomore",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Scout",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_10 && 16_Quest_16",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1604_0201_heronomore_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Title",
		"Description": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1604_0201_heronomore_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0101_ultimateintentions",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0101_d_00_container_ultimateintentions",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Scout",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_17",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0101_ultimateintentions_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Runeglass_Gem_Carnelian_Heal",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0101_ultimateintentions_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0201_strengthandweakness",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0201_d_00_container_strengthandweakness",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Scout",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_19",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_18",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0201_strengthandweakness_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 40,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0201_strengthandweakness_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0301_tribunetime",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0301_d_00_container_tribunetime",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Scout",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_19",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0301_tribunetime_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0301_tribunetime_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0401_headofsnake",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0401_d_00_container_headofsnake",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Scout",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_20",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0401_headofsnake_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1602_0401_2hBow_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0401_headofsnake_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0501_gloriamundi",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0501_d_00_container_gloriamundi",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1604_Charmion",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_22",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_21",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0501_gloriamundi_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0501_gloriamundi_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0601_secretssands",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0601_d_00_container_secretssands",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Marcella",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_23",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_22",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0601_secretssands_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0601_secretssands_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0501_miraclesmadness",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0501_d_00_container_miraclesmadness",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Marcella",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_24",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_23",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0501_miraclesmadness_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0501_miraclesmadness_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0601_hieratictruth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0601_d_00_container_hieratictruth",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Marcella",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_24",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0601_hieratictruth_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 80,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0601_hieratictruth_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0701_brokenkey",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0701_d_00_container_brokenkey",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Marcella",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_26",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_25",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0701_brokenkey_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_1605_0701_2hStaffFire_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0701_brokenkey_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0801_timecircles",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0801_d_00_container_timecircles",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Settlement",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_27",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_26",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0801_timecircles_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0801_timecircles_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "BrimstoneSandsArc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1602_0701_mightymustfall",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1602_0701_d_00_container_mightymustfall",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1602_Crassus_Settlement",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_28",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_27",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1602_0701_mightymustfall_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Title",
		"Description": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1602_0701_mightymustfall_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1605_0901_finalseal",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1605_0901_d_00_container_finalseal",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1605_Akila_Corsica",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_29",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_27",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1605_0901_finalseal_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Title",
		"Description": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1605_0901_finalseal_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_0901_secretindesert",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_0901_d_00_container_secretindesert",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v4p3",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_19 && 16_Quest_28 && 16_Quest_29 && 16_Quest_04",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_0901_secretindesert_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_0901_secretindesert_Complete_multi_01",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0902_queenrevealed",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0902_d_00_container_queenrevealed",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p6",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_16",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0902_queenrevealed_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0902_queenrevealed_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0902_queenrevealed_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0902_queenrevealed_Start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0902_queenrevealed_Proposal_multi_01",
		"InProgressResponse": "@NPC_Default_Dialogue_1624_01_Imhotep_v4p3",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0902_queenrevealed_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1625_0903_thecoronation",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1625_0903_d_00_container_thecoronation",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625a_Ghazi_p8",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_17",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1625_0903_thecoronation_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Title",
		"Description": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1625_0903_thecoronation_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1624_1101_tremorsinthesand",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "1624_1101_d_00_container_tremorsinthesand",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1624_Imhotep_v4p5",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Quest_31",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_18",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Title",
		"Description": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1624_1101_tremorsinthesand_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_01_Glyphs",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_01_d_00_container_Glyphs",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1665_Heron",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_06",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_01_Glyphs_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GlyphStone_Gift",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_01_Glyphs_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_02_MineScarabs",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_02_d_00_container_MineScarabs",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1641_Eudoxia",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_02_MineScarabs_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CarnelianT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_02_MineScarabs_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_03_HuntJackal",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_03_d_00_container_HuntJackal",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1642_Senhyris",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_03_HuntJackal_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_16_Side_03_1hRapier_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_03_HuntJackal_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_05_HuntLion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_05_d_00_container_HuntLion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1644_Nesse_outpost",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_05_HuntLion_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "FeatherT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_05_HuntLion_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_06_KillDynasty",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_06_d_00_container_KillDynasty",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1645_Xiaoling_cavalier_rest",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_03",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_06_KillDynasty_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_16_Side_06_2hMusket_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_06_KillDynasty_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_07_HelpHistorian",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_07_d_00_container_HelpHistorian",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1646_Froderico",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_04",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Schematic_House_HousingItem_Legion_Bookcase02_D",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_07_HelpHistorian_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_08_d_00_container_ClimbAqueduct",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1656_Perrin",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GlyphStone_River",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_08_ClimbAqueduct_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_10_BookofDead",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_10_d_00_container_BookofDead",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1649_Miresis",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Quest_17",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_10_BookofDead_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_JournalDescription",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_10_BookofDead_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_11_FeedIfrit",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_11_d_00_container_FeedIfrit",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1650_Flame",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GlyphStone_Food",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_11_FeedIfrit_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_12_GatherEggs",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_12_d_00_container_GatherEggs",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1651_Enez",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Side_16",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_12_GatherEggs_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "FoodSTRT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_12_GatherEggs_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_13_d_00_container_ScoutPyramid",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1652_Lysandra",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_TremorsSandwormQuest_Unlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_13_ScoutPyramid_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_16_d_00_container_UnlockTeleporter",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1656_Perrin",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_Side_08",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 20,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_16_UnlockTeleporter_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_17_HuntScorpion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_17_d_00_container_HuntScorpion",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1657_Tamouthis",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_08",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_17_HuntScorpion_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_19_HelpWarden",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_19_d_00_container_HelpWarden",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1659_Anna",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_30",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_19_HelpWarden_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "RuneCannonBlastT1",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_19_HelpWarden_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_20_HelpBastet",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_20_d_00_container_HelpBastet",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1660_Paubastis",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_20",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_07",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_20_HelpBastet_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "RawhideT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 50,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_20_HelpBastet_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_25_CactusFlower",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_25_CactusFlower_00_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1683_Zahur",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_25",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_25_CactusFlower_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Legion_Decor_FloorPlanter01_C",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlower_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlowerQuest_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlower_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlower_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlower_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_25_CactusFlower_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_26_SandThing",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_26_SandThing_00_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1684_Tahirah",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_26",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_01",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_26_SandThing_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "Runeglass_Case_Empty_Nature",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_26_SandThing_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_27_Redeem19th",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_27_Redeem19th_00_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1685_Acario",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_27",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_02",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_27_Redeem19th_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_16_Side_27_2hGreatSword_T5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_27_Redeem19th_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_28_LightsOut",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_28_LightsOut_00_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1686_Qabalah",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_28",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_03",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_28_LightsOut_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 80,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_28_LightsOut_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "16_Side_29_BathSalts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "16_Side_29_BathSalts_00_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1622_Innkeep",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "16_Side_29",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_03",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "16_Side_29_BathSalts_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "GlyphStone_Water",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Title",
		"Description": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Start",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@16_Side_29_BathSalts_Complete_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1601_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1601_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1602_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1602_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1603_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1603_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1604_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1604_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1605_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1605_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1607_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1607_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1608_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1608_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1609_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1609_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1610_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1610_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1611_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1611_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1612_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1612_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1613_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1613_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1614_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1614_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1615_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1615_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1616_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1616_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1617_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1617_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1618_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1618_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1620_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1620_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1621_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1621_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1622_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1622_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1623_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1623_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BrimstoneUnlock",
		"RequiredLevel": 60,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1624_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1624_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_09",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_1625_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_1625_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_01_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_01_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_02_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_02_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_03_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_03_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_04_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_04_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_05_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_05_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_06_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_06_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_07_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_07_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_08_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_08_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_09_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_09_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_10_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_10_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_11_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_11_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_12_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_12_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_01_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_01_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_02_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_02_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_03_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_03_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_04_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_04_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_05_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_05_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_06_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_06_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_07_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_07_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_08_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_08_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_09_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_09_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_10_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_10_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_11_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_11_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_12_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_12_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_01_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_01_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_02_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_02_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_03_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_03_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_04_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_04_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_05_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_05_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_06_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_06_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_07_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_07_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_08_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_08_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_09_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_09_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_10_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_10_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_11_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_11_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_12_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_12_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_16_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_05",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Hourly"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_16_EXP_14_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_16_EXP_14_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_C_16_EXP_14_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_C_16_EXP_14_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_S_16_EXP_14_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "FM_S_16_EXP_14_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 16,
		"RequiredAchievementId": "16_BSMSQ_10",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "1689_EXP_Coins_Objective",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": true,
		"Task": "1689_EXP_Coins_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1689_Roman_2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "1639_EXP_Coins",
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "1689_EXP_Coins_Success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@1689_EXP_Coins_title",
		"Description": "@1689_EXP_Coins_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1689_EXP_Coins_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1689_EXP_Coins_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1689_EXP_Coins_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1689_EXP_Coins_complete",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@1689_EXP_Coins_Cooldown",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	}
]